== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(Raj:)Hey, you think
it'd be okay
(Raj:)if I brought Claire
to the wine tasting?
(Leonard:)Sure. I'd like to meet her.
Oh, that's great.
(Raj:)I've been wanting her
to meet you guys, too,
(Raj:)so this seems like
the perfect opportunity.
(Sheldon:)Oh, but I won't be there.
(Raj:)Funny how that worked out.
(Leonard:)Does this mean Emily's not
in the picture anymore?
(Raj:)No, I'm still dating her.
(Leonard:)Okay, help me out.
(Leonard:)How are you doing this?
(Leonard:)Do they know about each other?
(Raj:)They know that
we're not exclusive,
(Raj:)and we just don't ask
too many questions.
(Sheldon:)You know, it's like how I play
Warlords of Ka'a with you
(Sheldon:)and Elder Sign with
Frank and Alicia.
(Leonard:)Who's Frank and Alicia?
Y... You and I spend
a lot of time together.
(Sheldon:)Can there be a little
mystery between us?
WOLOWITZ:
Okay.
(Howard:)Everything's hooked up.
We're ready.
(Sheldon:)I am going to record
this for posterity.
(Leonard:)All right, here goes nothing.
(Sheldon:)Here goes nothing?
(Sheldon:)This is the initial test
of our prototype.
(Sheldon:)Can we give it
a little more gravitas?
LEONARD:
Fine.
(Leonard:)Preliminary trial
of the infinite persistence
gyroscopic navigational system:
phase one commencing.